lottoleader.com 2016-06-23

# Privacy Policy | LottoLeader

**Privacy Policy**  
WiWine Services Ltd. (the ” Company “, ” us “, ” our ” or ” we”) is committed to protecting both your privacy and personal or general information such as information that can be directly associated with or used to identify a specific person or entity such as a name, address, telephone number, e-mail address or IP address or other such information. (the “personal Information”). The privacy policy (the “Policy”) outlined below details which information is collected from you when you use our website and services; how said information is collected; and how it is subsequently used. Please read this Policy in conjunction with our Terms & Conditions.  
By creating or using an Account or accessing and using the Website or Services, you agree to be bound by this Policy. If you do not agree to any of the provisions as set hereunder in this Policy, you have no right to use the Website or Services. This Policy should be read together with the Terms of Service and together they constitute the entire agreement between you and us. This Policy and the Terms of Service may be updated from time to time and therefore we ask you to check back periodically to read the most updated Policy. The most current version of the Terms of Service is available at Terms & Conditions. Your continued use of the Website and/or Services shall be deemed to be your continued acceptance of the terms of this Privacy Policy, as amended. Terms that are capitalized in this Policy and not defined herein shall have the meaning set forth in the Terms of Service.  
**Collection of Information**

**1\. Personal Information**  
The Company or others on our behalf may collect save or otherwise keep in our possession Personal Information from each User, including full name, date of birth, mailing address, email address, phone number, ID number, bank account information and proof of residence.  
**2\. Non-Personal Information**  
The Company or others on our behalf may also collect, save or otherwise keep in our possession Non-Personal Information that does not identify you personally, such as your sex, age and your history of use of the Website and/or Services.  
**3\. Additional Information.**  
The Company or others on our behalf may also collect, save or otherwise keep in our possession certain information that your browser sends to every Internet website you visit, such as your IP address, your browser information (including browser type, capabilities and language), your operating system, the date and time you accessed the website, certain location-based data, and the website from which you linked to the Website and/or Services.  
By using the Website and/or Services, you voluntary agree to provide us with any information, and to collect, save or otherwise keep in our possession such information (including Personal Information). If you refuse to provide us such information you may not have access to all functionality of the Website and/or Services.  
Please note that while we make reasonable efforts to secure all information and Accounts, it is impossible to have the information and Accounts completely secure. As such, we cannot accept any liability for the disclosure of Personal Information as a result of unauthorized access to our system, Software, Website or Accounts.  
You hereby undertake to provide accurate and up-to-date Personal Information whenever this is requested. Following any changes in your Personal Information, please notify us immediately at Contact Us.

**Use of Information**  
1\. We use the Personal Information collected from or about you in order to enhance and deliver our Services, provide reliable User support, process User requests, meet business requirements, and for all other purposes directly or indirectly related to the operation of our Website and Services. The Company maintains the right to disclose your Personal Information to any third parties that provide services to us. We further maintain the right to use your Personal Information in order to send personalized or targeted promotional offers, information, products, and services provided by us or selected third parties, with the purpose of improving your user experience and enhancing our customer service. We will not send you such messages if you opt-out from receiving such promotional messages, or at any time request by emailing us to this effect at Contact Us and/or by clicking the unsubscribe link on emails sent to you to stop receiving such promotional messages.

2\. We may also use your Personal Information for internal purposes, with the intention of evaluating and improving our Services and Website.

3\. By analyzing all information we receive, we may compile statistical information across a variety of users (the “Statistical Information”). Statistical Information helps understand trends and customer needs so that new services can be considered and so the Services and associated services can be tailored to User desires. We may share Statistical Information with our partners, pursuant to commercial terms that we determine in our sole discretion. In addition, we may provide any information to third parties, so long as we have removed any information that identifies any specific individual or user, such as a name, address or contact information.

4\. The Company may disclose your Personal Information if required to do so by law, or in cases where we believe that such action is necessary in order to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process, as well as to protect and defend our or the public’s rights and property. We reserve the right to share your Personal Information with any relevant company or agency if we suspect that you have attempted or succeeded to cheat or defraud us, or if we suspect you of committing any fraudulent or illegal activity.

5\. The Company may transfer and store your Personal Information in a country outside of your place of residence. In case the data protection laws in the storing country are less comprehensive than those in your country of residence, we will take steps to ensure appropriate protection of your Personal Information. Access to our Website and Services is restricted to individuals of legal age (18 years old or higher, if so specified in the user’s jurisdiction). We may make efforts to uncover attempts by minors to access our services, and this may require accessing and verifying your Personal Information. Any Personal Information that we discover was submitted by individuals not of legal age will be removed from our records.

**Cookies**  
We (or others on our behalf) use a browser feature known as cookies, which are small text files which are placed on your computer or equipment when you visit certain online pages, to track your activities, record your preferences, and make our site more responsive to your needs by delivering a better and more personalized experience to you. The cookies are stored on your computer’s hard drive and are used by us to help track your clicks and pass information as you go through the pages within our website. Cookies can allow us to associate navigational information from browsing visits with Personal Information you provide at our site.

**Security**  
The Company has taken reasonable security precautions and measures to protect and safeguard your Personal Information from unauthorized access or modification, improper use or disclosure, unlawful destruction, or accidental loss. Any third party with access to your Personal Information is obligated to respect the confidentiality and security. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. We will delete any Personal Information provided to us by a User upon the receipt of a written request by such User. We cannot restore information once it has been deleted.

**Links to Other Sites**  
Our site may contain links to other sites, and may be accessible from other websites via links. We are not responsible for the use of any data by third parties, and we cannot vouch for the privacy policies of any third party. We have no control over third-party sites or services, and all use of third-party sites or services is at your own risk. We cannot accept responsibility for the privacy policies of any such sites. We are not responsible for content available by means of such sites or services. We do not endorse any services or offered by third parties and we urge our users to exercise caution in using third-party sites or services. When we provide information to third parties, we remove any information that identifies any particular individual or user, such as a name, address or contact information, but we cannot provide complete assurance that the recipient will not be able to associate such de-identified information with a particular individual.

**Information Transfer**  
In the event of a sale, assignment, transfer, or merger with or to a third party, or if we file for bankruptcy or become insolvent, we may transfer your Personal Information to the relevant third party. We will fully cooperate with any law enforcement authorities or court order requesting or directing us to disclose the identity or behavior of any User suspected to have engaged in illegal behavior. We may use subcontractors that are located in countries other than your own, and send them information we receive. For example, we may send your information to any countries outside the United States, Canada or the European Union. Some our subcontractors may be subject to non-disclosure and non-use obligations. Nevertheless, some countries may have levels of protection of personal and other information which are not as high as in your country of residence or business. We may transfer our databases containing information if we sell our business or part of it.

**Disclaimer**  
Our Services operate without liability of any kind, and the Company takes no responsible for events or incidents beyond our direct control. We do not claim or guarantee that our handling of your Personal Information will be error-free, and we will not be held accountable or liable for any indirect, incidental, consequential, or punitive damages relating to the use or release of Personal Information.

**Questions**  
You may direct questions concerning this Policy by email to [Contact Us](https://lottoleader.com/contact-us/)  
by adding the word ‘privacy’ in the subject line.

**AML Policy**  
LottoLeader does not tolerate money laundering and supports the fight against money launderers. LottoLeader follows the guidelines set by the UK’s Joint Money Laundering Steering Group. The UK is a full member of the Financial Action Task Force (FATF), the intergovernmental body whose purpose is to combat money laundering and terrorist financing. LottoLeader now has policies in place to deter people from laundering money. These policies include:  
• ensuring clients have valid proof of identification

• maintaining records of identification information

• determining that clients are not known or suspected terrorists by checking their names against lists of known or suspected terrorists

• informing clients that the information they provide may be used to verify their identity

• Closely following clients’ money transactions

• Not accepting cash, money orders, third party transactions, exchange houses transfers or Western Union transfers.

Money laundering occurs when funds from an illegal/criminal activity are moved through the financial system in such a way as to make it appear that the funds have come from legitimate sources. Money Laundering usually follows three stages:  
• Firstly, cash or cash equivalents are placed into the financial system

• secondly, money is transferred or moved to other accounts (e.g. futures accounts) through a series of financial transactions designed to obscure the origin of the money (e.g. executing trades with little or no financial risk or transferring account balances to other accounts)

• And finally, the funds are re-introduced into the economy so that the funds appear to have come from legitimate sources (e.g. closing a futures account and transferring the funds to a bank account).

Trading accounts are one vehicle that can be used to launder illicit funds or to hide the true owner of the funds. In particular, a trading account can be used to execute financial transactions that help obscure the origins of the funds. LottoLeader directs funds withdrawals back to the original source of remittance, as a preventative measure. International Anti-Money Laundering requires financial services institutions to be aware of potential money laundering abuses that could occur in a customer account and implement a compliance program to deter, detect and report potential suspicious activity. These guidelines have been implemented to protect Lottoleader and its clients. For questions/comments regarding these guidelines, please contact us at support@lottoleader.com.
